### Louise Anna Marshall

64 Broadlands, Meltham, Holmfirth, HD9 5QY

Tel: 07841 652301

Email: <u>info@lmpersonaltraining.co.uk</u> Website: www.lmpersonaltraining.co.uk

## **Career Objective**

My goal is to achieve excellence in my field and to grow and adapt with the ever changing health and fitness industry. I aim to inspire and educate people on the benefits of exercise and healthy living.

My passion for the fitness industry and personal training grew following a 10 year career as a professional dancer. During which time I had to overcome and manage various injuries and understand now more than ever the importance of looking after the one body you have!

As an NASM Level 3 qualified trainer, I will inject fun into a clients sessions whilst achieving results quicker and safer than training alone giving your customers the direction and tools they need for a happier healthier lifestyle.

I always ensure to utilise my performance experience in all my contact with the public and clients.

I plan to extend my skill set further by training as a pilates instructor in the near future.

# Qualifications

#### **NASM**

- Level 3 Personal Trainer
- Pre and Post Natal

## LES MILLS

- Body Pump
- Body Combat
- CX Worx
- Grit Cardio, Strength and Plyo

#### ADDITIONAL

- Exercise Referal
- Lifetime Level 2 Gym Instructor
- Exercise to Music
- MMA Conditioning
- Circuit Training
- Training With Adolescents
- ISTD Associate Teacher in Ballet, Modern, National and Tap Dance

## **Education**

I was educated at St Johns RC Comprehensive School in Gravesend Kent.

I then studied for three years at Northern Ballet School in Manchester from the age of sixteen.

# **Work Experience**

#### **Current Employment**

Personal Trainer (Kirklees Active Leisure and Private)

• Les Mills Class Instructor (Huddersfield University and Kirklees Active Leisure)

## **Previous Employment**

- Fitness Instructor (Kirklees Active Leisure) 2011-2013
- Health Coach (PROHMS Health Academy) 2010-2011
- Gym Manager (Heritage Health Academy) 2008-2010